Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records, 1918-1974 (PPFA I)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Series VI. CORRESPONDENCE
  - Individual
    - Romilly, Dinky1964 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Rose, Florence1939-1944 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Rose, Dr. Kenneth
      - 1938-1951 (Box 69, Folder 9-10)
      - Biographical (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Broadcasts1943 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Reports and Trips1939-1946 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Speeches1940-1947 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Russell, Bertrand1950 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Salter, Katherine Hayden1943-1944 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Samstag, Renée1944-1947 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Sanger, Margaret
      - Articles1922-1951 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Autobiography (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Autobiography (Condensed Version)1941 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence1943-1950 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Publicity1938-1949 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Tour of Massachusetts1940 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Scribner, Dr. Charles E.1948 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Scull, James H.1942-1945 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Seibels, Dr. Robert E.
      - 1939-1944 (Box 71, Folder 1-4)
      - Publicity, Reports, Speeches1939-1941 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Report and Manual1941-1942 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Shedlovsky, Dr. Leo1939-1940 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Siegfried, Andre1925 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Simmons, Andrew1941-1942 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Simon, Caroline K.1939-1940 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Ruth1935-1938 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Ruth, Reports1937 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Stephenson, C.S.1941-1944 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Stevens, Helen Kennedy1936-1941 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Stoeker, Dr. Helena1942 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Stone, Dr. Abraham1959 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Stone, Dr. Hannah M.
      - Memorial Fund1941; 1948 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Publications1933-1941 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Stossel, Mildred1940-1945 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Stoughton, Philip1937-1944 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Streit, Clarence K.1944 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - StrutherJan, 1941 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Sullivan, Mark1943 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Sunnen, Joseph1956 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Taft, Charles P.1942-1945 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Taft, Horace D.1940-1942 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Talbot, Emily P. H.1941-1942 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Teel, Harold M.1939 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Thompson, Dorothy1934-1943 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Thompson, Warren S.1942-1945 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Timme, Ida Helen Haar1940 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Topping, Ruth1934 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Trent, Katherine1939-1943 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Trent, Katherine, Reports1939-1945 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Turberg, Jessie1942-1946 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Tweed, Harrison1940-1949 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Upham, J.H.J.1943 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Valiant, Margaret1941-1944 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Vander Veer, Dr. Adrian H.1946-1947 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Van Loon, Hendrik Willem1939-1942 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Van Slyck, Katharine R.1943 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Vogt, William1956-1959 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Ware, Dr. H. Hudnall1938-1944 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Weiss, Dr. Edward1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Wessels, Dr. Marie1939-1942 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Whitenack, Janet B.1938-1942 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Wickham, Bernice1938-1942 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Wile, Dr. Ira S.1937-1943 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Williams, Dr. Philip F.1940 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Williams, Dr. R. C.1939 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Wood, Mabel Travis1939-1940 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Worthy, William1958 (Box 74, Folder 18)
- Series VII. SUBJECT FILES
  - Abstracts, Maternal Health1939-1947 (Box 75, Folder 1-6)
  - Advertising
    - Birth Control1940-1943 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Clinics, Public Health Institute1937 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Commercial Contraceptives1934-1943 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper AdvertisementMarch 1941 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Airlines, American Airlines1940-1945 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - American Congress on Obstetrics and Gynecology, First1939 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - American Congress on Obstetrics and Gynecology, Second1942 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education1943-1947 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - American Education Fellowship1944-1947 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - American Eugenics Society (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - American Genetic Association1935-1944 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - American Magazine1944-1946 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - American Medical Association
    - Committee to Study Contraceptive Practices and Allied Problems1935-1937 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Convention (San Francisco)1946 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Council on Industrial Hygiene1942-1944 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Council on Medical Education and Hospitals1937-1943 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Council on Pharmacy and Chemistry1935-1946 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Council on Physical Therapy1943-1946 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Article1933-1943 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Scientific Exhibits1938-1947 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - American-Soviet Friendship, Inc.1944-1946 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - American Theater Wing, "Sunday Afternoon," 1946-1947 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - American Youth Commission1936-1941 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Anderson Chemicals, Inc.1939-1948 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Arc Diaphragm1941-1943 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Argosy1944-1949 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Babson's Statistical Organization1940 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Bach Products1940-1941 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Bilco Products Corporation1939-1941 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Birth Control
    - Articles on1931-1944 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Clippings1932-1935 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
    - Clippings regarding religious views1930s (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - History1931-1953, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 4-8)
    - History, Encyclopedia Articles1939-1952, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 9-12)
    - History, Pamphlet Material1917-1946, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 13-14)
  - "Birth Control and Public Policy" 1965 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Birth Control and War1940-1946 (Box 79, Folder 1a)
  - Birth Control and War, State League Responses1942-1943 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Birth Control Information Center1933-1934 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Birth Control Number, Unity1935 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Blind Societies for the Blind1937-1951 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Blind Society for the Prevention of Blindness1935-1949 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - By-laws, Standard Form to Become a NY State Corporationn.d. (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Child Study Association1928-1947 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Citizen's Committee for Planned Parenthood (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Clinical Medicine1939-1942 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Clinico Products (Dr. LeMon Clark)1938-1939 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Clinics
    - Administration1934-1938 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Answers and Follow-ups to Questionnaire1947 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Articles1929-1942 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Charts and Reports (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Comparative Studies1947 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Distribution1925-1950 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Fact Finding Survey1938 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Grants from American Birth Control League1939 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Manual for Standard Practice1933-1948 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Manual, Drafts1944 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Minimum Standards For1936, 1948 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - National Clinic Service1938-1944 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - National Clinic Service, Case History Card1938-1942 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Post-Graduate Institute on Clinic Procedures1940 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Referral Physicians1945, 1947-1949 (Box 81, Folder 2-3)
    - Referral Physicians, Questionnaire1942-1947 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Reports1931-1934 (Box 81, Folder 5-6)
      - New Jersey1936-1937 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Record1934 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Dec. 1934 - Dec. 1936 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Contraceptive and Fertility Clinic Services1945 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - 1937 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Forms1936-1948 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Survey of State Contraceptive Programs1940 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Conferences
    - Fifth International Malthusian Conference1922 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Sixth International Neo-Malthusian and Birth Control Conference1925 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - World Population Conference1926 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Birth Control Conference1929 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Seventh International Neo-Malthusian and Birth Control Conference1930 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Fourth Congress of the World League for Sexual Reform1930-1932 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Conference on Tomorrow's Children, New England, Press Releases1930-1941 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - American Conference on Birth Control and National Recovery1934 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - American Conference on Birth Control and National Recovery, Data1934 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - New England Regional Conference, Boston, MA1936 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Conference of Social Work1938 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Conference on Tomorrow's Children, Southern1939-1940 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - National Conference on Family Relations1939-1947 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Conference on Tomorrow's Children
      - New England1940 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Southern1940 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Midwest1941 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Midwest, Correspondence1941 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - New England1941 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Southern1941 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - New England1942 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - National Conference on Prevention and Control of Juvenile Delinquency1946 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - National Conference of Social Work1952 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - United Nations World Population Conference1954 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - National Conference on Social Welfare1959 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Consumer's Union of United States, Inc.1937-1949 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Contraceptive Industry, Report onc.1937 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Department of Commerce, Questionnaire1937 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - East and West Association1945-1949 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Fairs
    - New York County Fair1941 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - New York Fair (State, Syracuse, N.Y.)1936-1941 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - New York World's Fair1939 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Parent's Exposition1928 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Philadelphia, Sesqui-Centennial1926 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco Fair
      - 1938-1940 (Box 85, Folder 7-8)
      - Public Progress Committee1939 (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - Publicity1939 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Tri-State Welfare Conference1939-1940 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Women's Arts and Industries1926-1931 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Films
    - All-Scope Pictures, Inc.1947 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - "Birth of a Baby," 1938 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Documentary Films Production, Inc.1941 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - "The Fight for Life," 1940 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Film Treatment1945 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Filmedia Corporation1945 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - "No Greater Sin," 1941 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - "No More Children," 1930 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Planned Parenthood Movie1948-1949 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Slides and films proposed1946 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Synopsis of Proposed Film1941 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Financial Secretaries Group1943-1946 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Free World1943-1945 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Greenbaum, Wolff, and Ernst
    - Articles and Clippings1938-1941 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence1938-1943 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Laws on Venereal Disease1939-1940 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Legal Opinions on Birth Control1937-1940 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Obscenity Issues1937-1941 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Opinions on Possibly Obscene Books and Pamphlets1937-1947 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Physicians' Forms to Recover Seized Birth Control1940 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - State Contraception Laws
      - Alabama1937 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Arizona1937-1940 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Arkansas1937-1938 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - California1937-1946 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Colorado1937 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Connecticut1937-1940 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Delaware1935-1938 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - District of Columbian.d. (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Florida1937 (Box 88, Folder 9)
      - Georgia1937 (Box 88, Folder 10)
      - Idaho1937-1938 (Box 88, Folder 11)
      - Illinois1937 (Box 88, Folder 12)
      - Indiana1937 (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - Iowa1937 (Box 88, Folder 14)
      - Kansas1936-1938 (Box 88, Folder 15)
      - Kentucky1937-1938 (Box 88, Folder 16)
      - Louisiana1937 (Box 88, Folder 17)
      - Maine1937 (Box 88, Folder 18)
      - Maryland1937 (Box 88, Folder 19)
      - Massachusetts1937-1940 (Box 88, Folder 20)
      - Michigan1937-1940 (Box 88, Folder 21)
      - Minnesota1937-1938 (Box 88, Folder 22)
      - Mississippi1937-1944 (Box 88, Folder 23)
      - Missouri1937-1938 (Box 88, Folder 24)
      - Montana1937-1938 (Box 88, Folder 25)
      - Nebraska1937-1938 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Nevada1937-1938 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - New Hampshire1937 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - New Jersey1937 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - New Mexico1937 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - New York1929-1937 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - North Carolina1937 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - North Dakota1937 (Box 89, Folder 8)
      - Ohio1937-1938 (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - Oklahoma1937 (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - Oregon1937 (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - Pennsylvania1937-1938 (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Rhode Island1937 (Box 89, Folder 13)
      - South Carolina1937 (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - South Dakota1937 (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - Tennessee1937 (Box 89, Folder 16)
      - Texas1937 (Box 89, Folder 17)
      - Utah1937 (Box 89, Folder 18)
      - Vermont1937 (Box 89, Folder 19)
      - Virginia1937 (Box 89, Folder 20)
      - Washington1937-1938 (Box 89, Folder 21)
      - West Virginia1937 (Box 89, Folder 22)
      - Wisconsin1937-1938 (Box 89, Folder 23)
      - Wyoming1937 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Holland, Rantos Co., Inc.1933-1947 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Holland, Rantos Project1940-1944 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Hychex Product1939-1947 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Hygeia Magazine1939-1947 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Hygiene
    - Correspondence1942-1949 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Federation Program1942-1943 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Pamphlets and Reports1942-1945 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Industrial Hygiene, U.S. Public Health Service1941-1948 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Infertility Questionnaire1945-1948 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Insurance, Liberty Mutual Insurance Co.1939-1943 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - John Price Johns Corporation (Box 91)
    - "A Survey and Plan for Fund Raising for the Birth Control Clinical Research Bureau and the National Committee on Federal Legislation for Birth Control" 1930 (Box 91, Folder 1-5)
    - "Survey, Analysis and Plan for Fund Raising for the American Birth Control League" 1937 November 1 (Box 91, Folder 6-11)
  - Johnson and Johnson Co., Inc.1938-1946 (Box 91, Folder 12-13)
  - Labor Advisory Group1947 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Labor Press Associates1940-1941 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Literature Exchange1939-1950 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Look Magazine1942, 1946-1947 (Box 92, Folder 4-5)
  - Lord and Thomas, Advertising Agency1941, 1942 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Lowell Lecture, "Morals and Medical Care," 1949 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Magazine of the Year1946-1948 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - March of Time1936-1938 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Maternity Center Association1938-1948 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Maternity Research Council1925-1930 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Medical Administration Service1941-1944 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Medical Research
    - 1943-1947 (Box 93, Folder 2-4)
    - Contraception, General1933-1942 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Contraceptive Jelly1935 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Foam Powder
      - 1937-1942 (Box 93, Folder 7-8)
      - Questionnaire1938 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Questionnaire1943 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Tulare, California1937-1939 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Lorophyn Jelly1944-1946 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Publications1938-1943 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Reports to the Committee on Human Reproductionn.d. (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Statistical Proposal1941 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Modern Industry1944 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - National Health Council
    - Correspondence1934-1943 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - 1949 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Local Health Units1947-1952 (Box 95, Folder 3-4)
    - National Conference on Chronic Diseases1949-1962 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - National Information Bureau1935 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - National Medical Committee on Federal and State Contraceptive Legislation1934-1941 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - National Medical Council, Misc.1935-1941 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - National Medical Council
    - 1942-1945 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Change of Name1935 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence1936-1942 (Box 96, Folder 6-7)
    - Membership Notices to Board of Directors1942 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Negroes1941 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Plan of Organization and Functions1944 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Questionnaire1940, 1944 (Box 96, Folder 11-12)
    - Reorganization
      - 1940-1941 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, and Acceptances of Old Members1941 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, and Acceptance of New Members, A-Z1941 (Box 97, Folder 3-4)
      - Membership Refusals of New Members1941 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - National Planning Association1942-1947 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - National Probation Association1939 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - National Research Council, Correspondence1943-1947 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - National Research Council, General1948 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - National Social Welfare Assembly1946-1947 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - National Women's Trade Union League1940-1950 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - New Era Letter Shop1941-1947 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - The New Generation1941-1948 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - News Exchange1944-1947 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers, General1941-1948 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers, New York Sun1935-1949 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Nixon, Stuart, and Baker1940-1941 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Ortho Products, Inc. (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Outside Appeals for Funds1947 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Population
    - 1938-1941 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - National Program1939-1948 (Box 98, Folder 4-6)
    - Council on Population Policy1934-1935 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - PPFA Pamphlet1940-1941, 1948 (Box 99, Folder 2-3)
    - Printed Material1940-1950 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Scripps Foundation1941 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Post War Planning Committee1942-1943 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Post War Planning Committee1943-1945 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Production Schedules1944 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Public Affairs Pamphlet, "Planning Your Family," 1947-1948 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Publicity1941 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Public Health Mailings1939-1941 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Radio
    - Association for Education by Radio1945 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Conferences5/10/44 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Discs1939-1940 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - "Freedom from Fear," 1940-1945 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - "Let's Put Planned Parenthood on the Air," n.d. (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Mailings1943; 1952 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - One Way Radio1946 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Poll on Birth Control1935 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Questionnaire1942 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Scripts
      - 1939-1944 (Box 100, Folder 5-6)
      - "Planned Parenthood on the Air," 1949-1950 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Radio-T.V. Campaign Kit1953 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Transcript Requests1943-1944 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Relief
    - General1937-1943 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - General Statistics1936-1937 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - National Health Survey, United States Public Health Service1938 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - "On Relief," "Youth on Relief," Federal Employment Relief Administration1935-1936 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Reports by the American Association of Social Workers1935-1939 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Unemployment Relief Census, Federal Employment Relief Administration1933 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Research Council on Problems of Alcohol1941-1947 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Saint John Associates1941-1946 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Sandman Corporation1940-1944 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Social Science Research Council1928; 1942 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Social Work
    - Local Committee Reports3/15/1946 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Mailing1943 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Case Work Histories1937-1940 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Agencies, Letters to PPFA re: Pamphlet1942 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Publicity Council1942-1943 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - State Reports1942-1943 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Spermatozoa1936-1941 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Sponsors1941-1949 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Sponsoring Committee, Acceptances1940 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Sponsoring Committee, Refusals1940 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - State Leagues
    - Connecticut, Grant from Joseph Sunnen1956-1958 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Memos1942-1947 (Box 103, Folder 2-3)
    - Financial Memos1943, 1945-46 (Box 103, Folder 4-5)
  - Sterilization
    - Abstracts1938-1941 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - "Mental Defectives"1920-1940 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Pamphlets (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Survey Magazine1937-1949 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Tabard Press1943-1947 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Testimonial Dinners1931-1935 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Toepfer, Anderson Promotion Service1944-1948 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Tuberculosis, National Tuberculosis Association1939-1947 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - United Mailing1943-1946 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Foreign Aid1959 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Organizations for National Defense, Inc.1941-1942 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Venereal Disease
    - Abstracts1938-1947 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Articles1935-1947 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Congenital Syphilis1940-1945 (Box 105, Folder 1-1a)
  - Venereal Disease and Pregnancy1939-1943 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - "Voluntary Parenthood," 1948-1950 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Waverly Press1940-1947 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology1942 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Women's Army Auxiliary Corps1943-1944 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Writer's War Board1944 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Young Women's Christian Association1938-1947 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, Health Education Handbook (Box 106, Folder 2)
- SERIES X. OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Scrapbooks of clippings about Margaret Sanger and birth control compiled by Martha R. Vandever1922-1937 (Box 107-108)
  - Clippings scrapbook1931-1939 (Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous oversize materials removed from files1916-1942, n.d. (Box 110)
  - Planned Parenthood exhibit cards1941 (Map-case Flat file drawer 14)
  - Oversize materials from General Literature catalogueslate 1930s-1940s (Map-case Flat file drawer 14)
  - Drawings by Dr. Robert Latou Dickenson (Map-case Flat file drawer 14)